Guide to the Walter Gardner Hall Papers, 1923-1990 MS 280
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: The Democratic Party, 1944-1976
  - Subseries B: Politicians, (1944-1976)
    - Bob Casey, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - William O. Cooper, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Fagan Dickson, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Albert Gore, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Francis L. Loewenheim - FDR Library, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - J. J. Pickle - Democratic congressional and senatorial dinner, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - A. R. (Babe) Schwartz, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Preston Smith, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Bob Armstrong, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Rex Braun, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Chet Brooks, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Jack Brooks, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Ed Clark, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Fagan Dickson, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Bob Eckhardt, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Ralph Gonzalez, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Fred Hofheinz, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Ray Holbrook, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Barbara Jordan, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Don Kennard, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Francis L. Loewenheim - FDR Library, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Ed Muskie, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Wright Patman, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Walter H. Richter, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Barefoot Sanders, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - A. R. (Babe) Schwartz, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Preston Smith, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Bob Armstrong, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Ben Barnes, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Lloyd Bentsen, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Dolph Briscoe, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Chet Brooks, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Jack Brooks, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Maria L. Canfield, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Bob Casey, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Joe Christie, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Ed Clark, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - William O. Cooper, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Fagan Dickson, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Bob Eckhardt, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Frances Sissy Farenthold, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Anthony W. Hall, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Bill Hobby, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Barbara Jordan, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Henry Jordan, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Jim Nelson, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Barefoot Sanders, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - A. R. (Babe) Schwartz, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Ruth A. Walraven, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Chet Brooks, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Jack Brooks, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Clark W. Thompson, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Jimmy Carter, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Eugene McCarthy, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 69)
- Series III: Ralph W. Yarborough, 1952 - 1979
  - Gubernatorial election, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - RWY - WGH personal correspondence re gubernatorial election, Fall 1953 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Campaign for governor - 1954 - RWY vs. Shivers (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - RWY - 1954; WGH to RWY (3) re loan (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - RWY re loan from Citizens State Bank, May, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - RWY correspondence with WGH re appreciation for support in 1954, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - RWY correspondence with WGH re organization of a building and loan association, July - Aug. 1955 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - RWY to WGH asking his support in the 1956 gubernatorial campaign, March 24, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - RWY - Opening speech by RWY - 1956 campaign, June 1, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - RWY - Campaign material, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - RWY clipping with note from RWY to WGH, Aug. 4, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - RWY re campaign finances for 1956 gubernatorial elections (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - RWY 1956 campaign in Galveston, Harris and Brazoria Cos. (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - RWY re convention dispute between Shivers and LBJ forces; RWY position, May 1956 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - RWY re campaign debt to Southwestern Bell Tel. and partisanship of that company, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - RWY to WGH expressing thanks for his aid, Sept. 13, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - List of contributors of $100.00 or more - 1956 campaign, Dec. 20, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Biography of Ralph Yarborough, candidate for the U.S. Senate, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - RWY - Public letter - 1957 campaign (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - WGH to Samuel C. Brightman, editor, The Democratic Digest, re campaign issues, March 13, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - RWY to Dr. N. E. Dudney, President, Nat. Ass. of Soil Conservation, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - RWY - Clyde Wood re 1957 Senate race (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - RWY - Senate campaign - Galveston Co.; Gulf Coast, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Southwestern Bell, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence of WGH - Creekmore Fath re election laws, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Clippings - 1957 Senate (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - RWY re victory in 1957 Senate race; letter of thanks RWY to WGH (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - May 4 Democratic dinner in Washington - Seated with RWY, March - May 1957 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Byron Skelton - WGH - Breakfast for RWY, May 1957 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - WGH - Ed Clark re Ralph Yarborough and Price Daniel, Nov. 1957 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - WGH - Thad Hutcheson re recent Senatorial campaign, April 12, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Cards for RWY mailing list, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Yarborough Dinner, June 15, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - RWY - re political issues that would gain RWY exposure, June - July 1957 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - RWY - WGH re backyard BBQ in Dickinson, oil issue, Aug. 1957 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Re RWY visit to Galveston Co. in November 1957 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - WGH - RWY re tax advantages of savings and loan associations, Nov. 25, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - RWY campaign returns by county, 1954 - 1957 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - WGH - RWY - Personal correspondence and requests, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Oil imports, March - May 1958 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1958 Senatorial campaign (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Interview with RWY - Galveston 1958 campaign (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Campaign funding - 1958 - Galveston (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - WGH to RWY re Sam Rayburn - 1959 rice acreage allotments, Aug. 7, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence RWY, WGH and Neal Pickett and C. Mann Gregg, Fall 1958 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - WGH - RWY and Chester Bowles re diplomatic service, Jan. 1959 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - WGH and RWY re Lee Brasfield - Armed Forces Reserve Program, Jan. - March 1959 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - RWY; WGH; Bob Bray - correspondence, March - Nov. 1959 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Speech by WGH at the Yarborough dinner, May 1959 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - WGH, C.M. Gregg, Bob Bray re NLRB, Spring 1959 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - RWY and WGH re committee to abolish the poll tax as a prerequisite to voting in Texas, Fall 1959 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - RWY to WGH re Hall's advice; importance of Hall; Maury Maverick, Sr., Feb. 17, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Dickinson Chamber of Commerce banquet - at which RWY spoke, Feb 12, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - WGH to RWY re sales tax on gasoline, Oct. 3, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - RWY - WGH, Neal Pickett: personal correspondence and requests, March - Dec. 1960 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Re RWY's role in 1960 Presidential campaign, Summer, Fall 1960 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - RWY - WGH re 1961 presidential inaugural, Dec. 1960 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Personal correspondence and requests RWY; WGH and Bob Bray, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Re tickets to the Ralph Yarborough Buffet - Rice Hotel, Dec. 6, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Personal correspondence and requests RWY - WGH, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - RWY and WGH - Percy Selden re necessity of government ably presenting its point of view, July - Aug. 1962 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - RWY and WGH re Sam Rayburn, Aug. - Sept. 1962 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - RWY to Washington Post re Billie Sol Estes and political independence, May 24, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - WGH, RWY, Alex Dickie - correspondence, Jan. - Sept. 1963 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Larry Goodwyn to WGH re politics in Texas; RWY upcoming election New Shapes in Texas Politics, Feb. 21, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Re RWY appreciation dinner, friends of RWY - Austin, Tx, Oct. 19, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Clippings RWY appreciation dinner, Oct. 19, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - RWY to WGH expressing his thanks for the dinner, Oct. 29, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Jim Wright; Robert Baskin of the Dallas Morning News; WGH re reaction to RWY dinner, Oct. 1963 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Creekmore Fath; H.S. Brown; WGH - Texas AFL-CIO Funds for the RWY appreciation dinner, Nov. 1963 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - RWY to the President re President's visit to Tx, Nov. 1963 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - WGH correspondence with and re RWY, Nov. - Dec. 1963 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - WGH - RWY re dinner in Austin for JFK, Nov. 22, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - WGH on JFK and the press, Nov. 26, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Leslie Carpenter article on bad feelings between LBJ and RWY, Dec. 1963 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Jim Wright to WGH re his decision not to run for the Senate; Franklin Jones to Jim Wright, Dec. 17, 1963 and Feb. 11, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Franklin Jones; Jim Phelps; WGH re Don Yarborough campaign for governor in 1964 and its effect on RWY's Senate race, Jan. - Feb. 1964 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Senatorial campaign, Jan. - May 2, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - RWY - WGH correspondence re Gordon McClendon's use of 50,000 Billie Sol Estes Lie; FCC, April - June 1964 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - WGH public letter in behalf of RWY to bankers of Texas, April 14, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - To the Friends of Senator Ralph Yarborough - rough draft, finished copy, March 16, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Re primary debts; June 15 appreciation dinner, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Robert Morris, Statements of Expense, April - May 1964 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Gordon McLendon, Statements of Expense, April - May 1964 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Jack Cox, Statements of Expense, April - May 1964 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - George Bush's Statements of Expense, April - May 1964 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Contributions - 1964 Democratic primary - RWY's Statements of Expense, April - May 1964 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Membership - Statewide Finance Committee, March - April 1964 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - RWY, Second Report to Secretary of State (contributions), May 4, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - County returns - Democratic primary, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Contributions for 1964 primary, March 16 - May 4 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - WGH, Lists of various names and addresses also phone numbers needed for campaign work, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Latané Temple - Temple family - role in RWY campaign, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - RWY - Byron Skelton, National Committeeman for Texas re upcoming election; Republican Party, July - Aug. 1964 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Contributions 1964 general election, May - Dec. 1964 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Re contributions to RWY campaign, Fall 1964 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Re 1964 campaign debts and expenses - General election, Nov. 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Master log - Invitations received by RWY, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - WGH - Paul G. Hervey; re Corpus Christi teachers for Johnson, role of RWY, Sept. - Oct. 1964 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Letters to Hunter McLean, State Chairman, Democratic campaign re condition of Galveston Co. party, Summer 1964 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Re Texas Professors Committee for Johnson - Yarborough - Connally; Frank E. Vandiver, Chairman; Louis P. Galambos, Secretary, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Al Lieberman; WGH re RWY campaign in Senior Citizens Voice, Fall 1964 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - General election, May 18 - Nov. 1964 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - WGH - RWY personal requests, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Re Current legislative controversy on sugar from Imperial Sugar Co., Oct. 1964 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Re appointment of Eddy Lee Humel to the Air Force Academy, Jan. 1964 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - News releases; statements made on behalf of RWY by LBJ, JFK, WGH, F. E. Vandiver and others, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Campaign publicity, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - RWY cocktail party, Dec. 21, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - RWY contributors and supporters, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - List of donors, appreciation dinner, June 15, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - RWY - WGH personal requests and correspondence, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Leon Jaworski - WGH, RWY re contribution; RWY's campaign deficit, Jan. - Feb. 1965 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - RWY - WGH re patronage; judicial appointments, June 1965 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - WGH - RWY re rumors of RWY seeking a federal judgeship, Oct. 1965 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Re proposition to make state offices four year terms, Nov. 1965 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - WGH, RWY, Bill Ballew re RWY address at the American Right of Way Luncheon, Dec. 3, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - WGH - R. E. Bob Smith re RWY dinner; contributions, June 4, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Re Senator's Club; holding the dinner on May 15, April 1965 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Re making up the list of potential donors to RWY June 4 dinner, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Re asking Dudley C. Sharp and Will Clayton to support the June 4 RWY dinner, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Lists of contributors and invited guests to the RWY dinner, June 4, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Alphabetical list of major RWY supporters - June 4 dinner, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Invitations to the June 4 dinner, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Jim Phelps, WGH re H. J., Don and R.W. Yarborough and Kemp vs. Harrison, Spring 1965 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - RWY special account - used to pay for investigation of a possible libel suit over Estes lie?, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - RWY - WGH; Earl I. Harwood; Franklin Jones; J. R. Parten re McClendon - Estes lie and possible libel suit, Spring/Summer 1965 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Re favorable articles on RWY in the Texas press, July 1965 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Proceeds of June 4 dinner; status of the Friends of Ralph Yarborough account, June 30, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Contribution to pay off campaign indebtedness, July 1965 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Re photographs of June 4 appreciation dinner, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Contributions to Friends of RY - June 4 dinner, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Thank you letters for June 4 dinner, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - WGH - RWY re Sam Low and reorganization of the Customs Service, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - WGH - RWY: personal requests and correspondence, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - RWY, WGH, Preston Poole re discrimination on the basis of color in the pay of county agriculture agents, Summer/Fall 1966 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - WGH, RWY; Max Peck re HR 13712 - minimum wage; hotel - motel industry, June 1966 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - RWY to Bill Ballew, WGH; Frank Vandiver re Veterans Bill; population control; pollution; American Liberties, March 7, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - RWY - LBJ re appointment of A. R. (Babe) Schwartz as U.S. District Attorney, June 29, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - WGH, Frank Vandiver, RWY re Dr. Tsanoff's speech: Intellectual Freedom, Spring 1966 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - WGH - RWY re HR 14159 (banking legislation), July 1966 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - WGH - RWY - Waggoner Carr re article by James McCrory implying Carr's reference to RWY in San Antonio speech, Aug. 4, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - J. R. Parten - WGH - RWY re New minimum wage law, Oct. 1966 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Re Gov. John Connally serving as Commissioner General for Hemisfair, July 1966 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - RWY - WGH: personal requests and correspondence, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Re integration of the Extension Service, Spring 1967 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Franklin Jones; WGH; RWY: appointment of Phillip Baldwin to a vacancy on the U.S. District Court, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Re Galveston Co. Democratic precinct chairmen, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Re tribute dinner for Ernest Gruening, March 1967 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Speech of Ralph W. Yarborough, U.S. Senator from Texas to a Joint Session of the Texas Legislature in the Texas Capitol, April 17, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Re RWY at V.F.W. convention, June 11, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Marion Meade, Senator Ralph Yarborough, He stands alone in the Lone Star State Coronet, June 1967 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - WGH - RWY re HR 7610 and SB 1314 - barge traffic regulation, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - RWY - WGH re National Flood Insurance, Summer 1967 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - WGH - RWY re Vietnam and LBJ's loss of political support due to the war, Fall 1967 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Disaster relief on the Texas Gulf Coast after Hurricane Beulah, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - RWY: letter in tribute to Forrest Smith, Andrews Tx; details of past campaigns in West Texas, Sept. 15, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - RWY - Bill McIntyre re National Railroad Workers strike; compulsory arbitration, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Re incident in El Paso between RWY and John Connally, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - RWY running for governor, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - March 1967 material used in making out the invitation list for June 13 dinner, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Re setting up June 13 RWY dinner, April 29, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Invitation lists for June 13 RWY dinner - Master list; preparation of invitation list; late additions, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - J. R. Parten list, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Warner Brock list, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Ed Clark list, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Cyril Smith list, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - WGH list, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - List of those attending and/or contributing to RWY dinner, June 13 - Houston, Tx., 1968 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Invitations to June 13 RWY dinner, tickets; ticket request cards, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Re photographs for RWY dinner June 13, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - RWY - WGH re Joe Tonahill's contribution to RWY dinner, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - WGH - notes and memos re RWY June 13 dinner, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - RWY, WGH and Bernard Rapoport re June 13 dinner, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Responses to invitations for RWY dinner, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Contributors and ticket purchasers for RWY dinner, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Bills and expenses of the RWY dinner June 13, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - RWY - WGH expressing his thanks for the dinner, June 18, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Name tags (alphabetical), extra tags, magic marker, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Alphabetical mailing list on 4 by 6 cards, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - RWY Day at Hemisfair, July 1968 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - WGH, RWY: personal requests and correspondence, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Bank Statements - Galveston Co. Yarborough Comm. and Johnson - Yarborough campaign fund, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - WGH - RWY re Johnny Criss, a labor leader and his vendetta against WGH, June 1968 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - RWY - Wayne Justice; Richard Brooks Hardee re their swearing in as a federal judge and U.S. district attorney and 1952 campaign, July 10, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - RWY - WGH re Friends of Ralph Yarborough account, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - WGH - RWY re Stuckey and Speer Inc., Diamond Importers, July/Aug. 1968 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - RWY - WGH re Hall's membership in the Texas Philosophical Society, Nov. 1968 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - WGH - RWY re Karla Stewart, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - RWY - WGH re Louis S. Riley, M.D., 1969 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - RWY - WGH re Ted Farmer, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - RWY - WGH re Kenneth Gentry, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - RWY - WGH: personal requests and correspondence, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Before VFW (packet), Spring 1970 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Photos campaign billboards (packet), Spring 1970 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Democratic primary, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Committee for good government, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Dickinson Friends of Yarborough acct. no. 560-838, Democratic primary, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Wegman Walker to WGH re RWY running as an independent in Nov. 1970, May 9, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Letters received by WGH re RWY's defeat on May 2, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Primary returns, May 2, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Letters received after primary defeat, May/June 1970 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Re July 15 appreciation dinner, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Re campaign debt, May/Aug. 1970 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - RWY - WGH re Commendatory letters received after primary defeat, Nov. 23, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - WGH - RWY personal correspondence and requests, June - Nov. 1970 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - WGH - RWY personal correspondence and requests, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - WGH - RWY re added value tax and ad valorem taxes, Feb. 14, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - RWY Appreciation Committee, July 27, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Re Democratic primary for U.S. Senate, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Democratic primary, Dickinson Headquarters, J. Abbott, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - RWY - WGH: personal correspondence and requests, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Letterhead, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - WGH - RWY: personal correspondence and requests, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - RWY: Committee for Good Government, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Clippings, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Election clippings, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Clippings, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Possibilities of RWY running for Gov. in 1966, Aug. 1965 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Clippings, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Clippings, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Clippings, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Clippings, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Clippings re Democratic primary, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Clippings, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Election clippings, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - WGH - RWY re RWY's political career, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- Series IV: Lyndon B. Johnson, 1947-1972
  - WGH to LBJ, Oct. 30, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Re Democratic primary LBJ vs. Coke Stevenson, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - General election Galveston County, Nov. 2, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - LBJ - WGH: personal requests and correspondence, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Re disputed election of 1948: LBJ - Coke Stevenson, 1948-52 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - LBJ - WGH: personal correspondence and requests, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - No title, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - No title, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Requests and 1952 elections (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - No title, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Democratic primary - personal requests, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - No title, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - No title, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - No title, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - No title, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Gulf Coast hamburger party honoring LBJ, Sept. 21, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - LBJ for President, Fall 1959 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Address to Citizens Awards Dinner, Nov. 29, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - LBJ for President dinner, June 13, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - LBJ for President, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Re WGH, Hall's Case for LBJ, The Texas Observer, 51 1 and 5, March 25, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - WGH - LBJ: personal correspondence and requests, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Campaign information for Kennedy - Johnson, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Democratic Digest Feb. - Dec.: Kennedy - Johnson, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Re Kennedy - Johnson campaign, July 1960/April 1961 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Encapsulated clipping How the County Voted by Precincts - Galveston, Nov. 8, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - WGH - LBJ: personal correspondence and requests, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - WGH - LBJ: personal correspondence and requests, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 13)